We worked so hard to build a swimming pool for the turtle
but it made a mess.  So
yesterday you saw that we caught a tortoise from the field and
we give it rice to eat but it does
not eat it.  Rest of the friends, you had
told in the comment that he eats soil, that is why
Munia and I brought him to the field and
left him in the soil.  He immediately
breaks the hole and hides.  Rest of the friends,
mother was also in the field and was harvesting paddy
and she told us that there is some water in the field,
so you should connect it to that small tractor.
So we flicked the switch.
And by pulling the rope and starting the tractor, they
plough their fields in a short time.
After that Munia takes out the tortoise from the mud
and says, brother, it has become very
dirty.  Let's give it a bath in the swimming pool.
So, we come home and fill the
swimming pool with air
and water along with the Munia gang and as soon as we put the turtle in it,
it starts swimming around in the water.
Seeing this, Anu becomes very
happy.  But then the turtle made
a hole in the swimming pool.
Due to which air starts coming out.
[music]